迈克:爸爸,瞧,
Mike: Dad, look, I need a favour,
我需要帮忙.我上晚课要迟到了,但是我的车发动不了.
I'm late for my night class and the car won't start.
杰森:好的,给.开我的.
Jason: Ok, here.Take mine.
迈克:真棒!
Mike: Great!
杰森:但是我的油差不多没有了.给你20块.
Jason: And I'm running low on gas.Here's a twenty.
迈克:哦,真好爸爸.谢谢.
Mike: Oh, gee whiz dad.Thanks.
麦琪:杰森,那可是迈克呀.
Maggie: Jason that was Mike.
杰森:当然是了.
Jason: It sure was.
开萝尔:你把你的车给他开?
Carol: You just gave him your car.
克莉丝:我甚至连玩具都不借给他.
Chrissy: I don't even lend him my toys.
杰森:行了.
Jason: Come on.He hasn't missed a single night class in three months.
三个月来他没有缺一次夜课.他终于想学习了.
He finally cares about school.
那我为什么不把我的车借给这样的年轻人呢?
Why would I not lend a young man like that my car?
克莉丝:可怜的蠢货.
Chrissy: The poor dumb shlum.
杰森:嗨.行了.如果你们鬼混了二十年,但是最终转变成迈克现在这样,你也可以借用我的车.
Jason: Hey.Com eon.If you guys screwed up for twenty years and finally turned
your life around like that, you can borrow my car too
本:行!
Ben: Aright!
杰森:麦琪,如果我说的话错了,就大声说出来.
Jason: And Maggie, if I am way off base here, just speak up.
麦琪:不在孩子面前.
Maggie: Not in front of the children.
杰森:凯特!
Jason: Kate!
凯特:嗨.
Jason: How are you?I haven't seen you for months.Look who's here.
杰森:你好吗?我几个月没见到你了.瞧,这是谁?
Kate: Hi.
麦琪:嗨.很高兴见到你.
Maggie: Hey.Nice to see you.
凯特:我也很高兴见到你.迈克在哪?
Kate: Good to see you too.Where is Mike?
开萝尔:他刚刚走了.
Carol: He just left.
本:是呀.
Ben: Yeah.In the car that dad is going to let me borrow if I can
开着那辆我只要再胡闹六年爸爸就让我借的车.
just screw up for another six years.
凯特:今天是星期二.今天晚上是我开.
Kate: It's Tuesday.It's my night to drive.
麦琪:今天晚上是不是有英语课?
Maggie: Is this fishnet stocking night a English class?
凯特:英语课?
Kate: English class?
麦琪:在波顿.你们俩都上夜校.
Maggie: At Boynton.You are both at night school.
凯特:我为什么要去波顿?我上真正的大学了.
Kate: Why would I go to Boynton?I went to a real college.
杰森:那么如果你和迈克不去上夜课,你们去哪?
Jason: Well if you and Mike aren't going to night class, where are you going?
凯特:过去三个月我们一直去的同样的地方.
Kate: Same place we've been going for the passed three months.
歌曲:人们说氖气灯光在百老汇辉煌.在百老汇.
Song: They say the neon lights are bright on Broadway.On Broadway.
他们说在天空中一直有神奇.在天空中.但是当他们 ……
They say there's always magic in the air.In the air.But when they...
迈克:凯特,你迟到了.
Mike: Kate, you are late.
凯特:你为什么不告诉我,你父母还不知道这工作?
Kate: Why didn't you tell me that you parents didn't know about this job?
迈克:因为我……什么?你在那里见到我父母的?
Mike: Because I...what?Where did you see my parents?
凯特:在你家.今天是星期二.轮到我开车.
Kate: At your house.It's Tuesday.It's my turn to drive.
迈克:哦,我的天.
Mike: Oh my gosh.
迈克和凯特:在百老汇.
Mike and Kate: On Broadway.
迈克:哦,糟了.现在他们知道我一直逃课了.
Mike: Oh great.Now they know that I have been skipping class.
凯特:对不起.你可以做的至少是道歉.
Kate: Excuse me.The least you could do is apologize.
迈克:为什么呀?
Mike: For what?
凯特:我觉得像个傻瓜,迈克.我被卷入你的谎言中了.
Kate: I felt like a fool Mike.I got caught in the middle of your lie.
迈克:那么我怎么办呢.我被卷入你的谎言中了.
Mike: What about me.I am caught in the middle of your lie.
凯特:好了.
Kate: Good.
妇女:你最好盖一下你的桌子.那个已经脏了.
Lady: You better cover your tables.It's getting ugly over there.
凯特:你知道在这段时间里幸亏我们没有约会.
Kate: You know it's at times like this that I am really happy we're not dating.
迈克:你什么意思呀?行了,我们每周都出去.
Mike: What do you mean?Come on, we go out every week.
凯特:不,我是说约会,约会呀.
Kate: No, I mean dating dating.
迈克:哦,你要我付帐?
Mike: Oh, you want me to pay?
凯特:迈克,你为什么必须对父母撒谎?
Kate: Mike, why did you have to lie to your parents?
你什么时候才能长大,告诉他们你是唱歌服务员?
When are you going to grow up and tell them that you are a singing waiter?
凯特:那么显然是今晚了.
Kate: Well apparently tonight.
杰森:亲爱的,我们想到的所有处罚,
Jason: Honey, all the punishments we have ever come up with,
没有一个管用的.
none of them have ever worked.
麦琪:那么你打算对他怎么处理?
Maggie: Well what are you going to do to him?
杰森:一些新的.一些大胆的.一些粗野的.现在你上楼去.请.
Jason: Something new.Something bold.Something wild.Now you go upstairs.Please.
麦琪:那我就上去,只要你把拨火棍给我,
Maggie: Well I will so long as you give me the poker.
迈克:啊!嗨,爸爸.
Mike: Uh, hey dad.Did you hear the news?
你听说那消息了吗?凯特曾经是病理性说谎而被送进精神病院.他不会买账的.
Kate's been institutionalized for being a pathological liar.
行了,迈克,
He's not going to buy that.Right Mike, it's time to face this like a man.
是时候像个男人来面对这件事情.晚安,爸爸.
Goodnight dad.
杰森:迈克.不不,来,来.坐下!快点,靠近火.
Jason: Mike.No no, come, come.Sit!Come on, by the fire.
迈克:啊,爸爸.拨火棍在哪呢?
Mike: Uh dad.Where's the poker?
杰森:妈妈拿上楼睡觉了.
Jason: Mum's got it upstairs in the bed.
迈克:哦
Mike: Oh.
杰森:坐下!
Jason: Sit!
迈克:好的.
Mike: Ok.
杰森:这火变的微弱了,是吧?
Jason: That fire's getting kind of low isn't it?
我猜你可能感觉奇怪,我为什么烧你的书.
I guess you are probably wondering why I am burning your books.
迈克:这些是我的书?
Mike: These are my books?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah.
迈克:爸爸.
Mike: Dad.
杰森:因为你从来没有去上夜校的课.
Jason: From that night school class you haven't been attending.
迈克:哦,啊,瞧,瞧,爸爸.我可以解释一切的.
Mike: Oh uh, look look dad.I can explain all this.
杰森:啊哈.迈克,你和我可不可以真诚的对待对方?
Jason: Uh hu.Mike can you and I just be honest with each other?
迈克:那么啊啊,恩,恩.我有点担心那些可能对我们的关系有影响,爸爸.
Mike: Well uh uh um um.I'm a little afraid of what that might do
to our relationship dad
杰森:我错了,迈克.我是百分之百的错了.
Jason: I've been wrong Mike.I've been a hundred percent wrong.
迈克:什么?
Mike: Pardon me.
杰森:我的错误是在于逼迫你上学.
Jason: I've been wrong about forcing you to stay in school.
迈克:哦,那么我猜我们应该早就尝试这坦诚的事情了.
Mike: Oh.Well I guess we should have tried this honesty thing a long time ago.
杰森:只是因为我有这样的想法,
Jason: Just because I've this thing,
而且我希望你在这不安全的世界有安全感,我认为你应该有个学位……这并不意味着你必须有同样的梦想.
and I want you to have security in this insecure world,
你的梦想是表演,
and I think you should have a degree...
迈克.
that doesn't mean you should have the same dream.Your dream is to act Mike.
我需要你百分之一千的追求这个梦想.干吧!
I want you to follow that dream one thousand percent.Do it!
我会永远站在你身后.
I'm behind you all the way.
迈克:在我后面多远?
Mike: How far behind me?
麦琪:亲爱的,你昨晚没有睡觉.
Maggie: Honey, you didn't come to bed last night.
杰森:你知道在早上五点曼哈顿没有车.
Jason: You know there is no traffic in Manhattan at five in the morning.
麦琪:你在曼哈顿干什么?
Maggie: What were you doing in Manhattan?
杰森:我需要去那里,麦琪,
Jason: I need to be there Maggie to pick up my copies of Variety, Backstage,
去整理我的杂耍,后台和角色分配方面的书.
Casting Call.
麦琪:哦,那么迈克说服你也去当演员,是吗?
Maggie: Oh, so Mike convinced you to become an actor too, did he?
杰森:麦琪,这是迈克的希望和梦想.
Jason: This Maggie is Mike's hopes and dreams.And this is the real world.
而这是现实世界.有什么问题吗?
Any questions?
迈克:妈妈,爸爸,
Mike: Mum, dad, my alarm clock just went off at six am.
我的闹钟停在上午6点钟不动了.现在我甚至没闹钟了.
I don't even have an alarm clock.
杰森:哦,你现在有了,迈克.早饭.坐!坐!
Jason: Oh, you do now Mike.It's breakfast.Sit!Sit!
迈克:啊?
Mike: Hu?
杰森:迈克的希望和梦想加熏肉.来吧,
Jason: Mike's hopes and dreams with bacon.Come on son.
儿子.当你吃的时候,看看这些.
And while you are eating, take a look through these trades.
那是你们演员这么称呼的,是吗?
That is what you actors call them, isn't it?
迈克:是呀.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:这里,迈克.
Jason: Right here Mike.
我已经圈了一些东西,我认为你可能适合.
I've circled a few things that I thought you might be right for.
迈克:妈妈!
Mike: Mum!
麦琪:我不知道.
Maggie: I don't know.
迈克:爸爸,现在谈论角色是不是有点早?
Mike: Dad, isn't this a little early to be talking about auditioning?
杰森:来吧!如果你打算寻求梦想的话,你必须行动起来去追求梦想,
Jason: Come on.If you are going to go for it,
瞧这?需要一个可爱的,
you've got to get up and go for it.Look at this?
不负责任的捣蛋鬼.麦琪,是我们的儿子.
Looking for a lovable, irresponsible doofus.Maggie, it's our boy.
麦琪:也许不仅仅是他.
Maggie: Maybe not just him.
迈克:我能演这个.
Mike: I could play this.
杰森:当然你能行.里面还有数百个.快点,拿上这些,走吧.
Jason: Of course you could.There are hundreds of them in there.
走,走,走,走,走!
Come on, take these, get going.Go, go, go, go, go!
迈克:行.
Mike: Alright.
杰森:等一下,你需要一些午饭的钱.
Jason: Wait a minute, you are going to need some lunch money.
迈克:哇.
Mike: Wow.
杰森:行.
Jason: Alright.
迈克:谢谢爸爸.
Mike: Thanks dad.
杰森:是,是,有效了,麦琪.
Jason: Yep yep, it's working Maggie.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
杰森:有时候我吓了自己.
Jason: Sometimes I frighten myself.
麦琪:小甜心,这是我们的婚姻.这是我们的计划.有问题吗?
Maggie: Sweetheart, this is our marriage.This is your plan.Many questions?
迈克:嗨,我是迈克 西维尔.我来这试演角色……
Mike: Hi, I'm Mike Seaver.I'm here to read for the part of the...
接待:可爱的,不负责任的捣蛋鬼.
Receptionist: The lovable, irresponsible, doofus.
迈克:我是天生的.
Mike: I'm a natural.
接待:我们一小时以后开始.制片会迟点到.
Receptionist: we are running and hour late.The producer is getting a little behind
迈克:哦哦,没关系.我不着急.我也没什么地方去.
Mike: Oh oh, no problem.I'm in no hurry.I've got no place else to go.
接待:真可怜.
Receptionist: That is so sad.
迈克:这才是糟透了,我上学接受教育.
Mike: It could be a lot worse.I could be in school getting an education.
男人:我听到你说了.
Man: I hear you.
迈克:哦,嗨,
Mike: Oh hey, hey hey!
嗨嗨!那不是演老的话剧"法律力量"的着名演员嘛?
Isn't that that famous actor from that old show "Law Force"?
男人:我不知道.我只看公共广播公司.
Man: I don't know.I only watch PBS.
迈克:是的,是他.是来昂内尔 道格拉斯.我没有错过一个情节.
Mike: Yeah, that's him.that's Lionel Douglas.I never missed an ep isode.
他是值得敬畏的.那,那,
He was awesome.Well, well, well.Freeze!
那.别动!在触犯法律之前,你应该好好想想.
You should know better that to mess with the Law Force.
来昂内尔:很好,孩子.
Lionel: That's pretty good kid.
迈克:我知道.来昂内尔 道格拉斯!等等,我告诉我妈我见到了你.哦,她认为你拥有最健美的臀部.不是我说的.不.我是说男人的那种.你知道的.
Mike: I knew it.Lionel Douglas!Wait till I tell my mum that I met
you.Oh she thinks you have got the cutest butt.Not that I don't.No
I mean that in a manly kind of way.You know
来昂内尔:放松,孩子.你快要爆炸了.
Lionel: Easy kid.You are going to explode.
迈克:你也像普通人一样有幽默感,太好了.啊,
Mike: You've got a sense of humour like regular people.that's great.
哇哇,你不是来试演那个可爱的捣蛋鬼的角色吧,对吗?
Ah, wa wa, you're not reading for the part of the lovable doofus are you?
因为如果我和你试演竞争,我就没有机会了.
Cos if I'm reading against you I don't stand a chance.
我是说,瞧,我可不想羞辱我自己.
I mean look, I don't ant to humiliate myself.
Lionel: Kid.Relax.Would an EMMI award winning star of his own prime time
在他事业的巅峰时期,会来试演一个小角色吗?想想.
television series be reading for a bit part?Think.
迈克:关于什么?哦,不,当然不会.
Mike: About what?Oh, no, of course not.
来昂内尔:瞧,事实上他们为增加了一个新的男主角,
Lionel: See actually they are adding a new leading man to the Big City
所以如果我看上剧本,我可能出演.
Secrets, so if I like the script thing might happen.
迈克:好呀.
Mike: Ok.
来昂内尔:你需要真的注意你做什么样的电视.
Lionel: You've got to be real careful what kind of television you do.
迈克:我就一个,只拍彩色的.
Mike: I for one only do colour.
接待:道格拉斯先生.
Receptionist: Mr.Douglas.
来昂内尔:对.哦,嗨,孩子.祝你好运.你会演好捣蛋鬼.
Lionel: Yes.Oh hey kid.Good luck.You'll make a great doofus.
杰森:呵呵呵.我饿得能吃下一匹马.我运气好.
Jason: Ho ho ho.I'm so hungry I could eat a horse.I'm in luck.
麦琪:和你儿子玩智力游戏让你晕头转向.
Maggie: Well playing mind games on your son sure makes you giddy.
杰森:我忍不住.对不起,我只是想像所有那些门都对他关闭,我就起鸡皮疙瘩.这,摸一下.
Jason: I can't help it.I'm sorry, I just imagine all those doors being slammed
in his face and I get goose bumps.Here, feel
麦琪:为什么你不让自己去?也许被巴士撞了.
Maggie: Why don't you let yourself go?Maybe he got hit by a bus.
杰森:希望是学校巴士.我在开玩笑,麦琪,但是我们没有选择.
Jason: Hopefully the school bus.I'm kidding Maggie, but we had no choice.
麦琪:我们!问过我吗?
Maggie: We!I wasn't consulted.
杰森:没和你商量的因为我想你不会同意.
Jason: The reason I didn't consult you was that I didn't think you'd agree
with me.
麦琪:见鬼,对,
Maggie: Well damn right I wouldn't agree.
我不会同意.我感到难受,希望我儿子失败,.
It makes me feel bad to wish for my son's failure.
杰森:亲爱的,演戏是他的梦想,
Jason: Honey with his dreams of acting and the odds against that,
但是没有这样的机会,他只会毁掉他的希望和梦想.
he's just going to have his hopes and dreams crushed.
毁灭他的最佳人选,当然是最爱他的人.
And who better to crush them that the people who love him most?
麦琪:对,也许当他发现梦想不能实现的时候,
Maggie: Well maybe if he finds out that sometimes your dreams don't work out,
他最终会专心地读书.
he'll finally concentrate on school.
杰森:那么我们同意了?
Jason: So we are agreed?
麦琪:是,我们同意了.
Maggie: Yeah, we are agree.
杰森:现在当他回家的时候低落,消沉和痛心什么的,
Jason: Now when he comes in here all disappointed and down and hurting
你千万别笑.
and everything, don't you go giggling.
麦琪:我不会的.
Maggie: I won't.
杰森:好.哈哈哈.有时候我喜欢当父母.
Jason: Good.Ha ha ha.Some days I love being a parent.
迈克:爸爸,妈妈.
Mike: Mum, dad!
杰森:想想糟糕的事情,想想糟糕的事情.
Jason: Think bad thoughts, think bad thoughts.
迈克:妈妈,爸爸,
Mike: Mum, dad, the best news you've ever heard in your whole life.
这是你们一生中听到的最好的消息.妈妈,我绝不开玩笑.
And mum, that's not an age joke.
杰森:是什么?
Jason: What is it?
迈克:好吧,爸爸,
Mike: Ok dad, remember that soap opera audition you told me about?
还记得你叫我去试演那个肥皂剧吗?可爱的捣蛋鬼?
For the part of the lovable doofus?
杰森:你得到了那个角色,是吗?
Jason: You got the part, didn't you?
迈克:不,不.我是可怕的捣蛋鬼.
Mike: No, no.I was a terrible doofus.
杰森:感谢上帝.别那样吓着我.
Jason: Thank god.Don't scare me like that.
迈克,但是听着,
Mike: But look, they said that I had something special.
他们说我有独特之处.
They said I was an interesting type.
他们说我很有意思.他们还说让我在扮演新男主角.
They said that I am the new leading man on Big City Secrets!
麦琪:哇!哇!哇!好呀!
Maggie: Wo!Wo!Wo!Yeah!
迈克:是呀.爸爸,我把这都归功于你.
Mike: Yeah.Dad and I owe it all to you.
开萝尔:妈妈想知道你是不是真的不吃晚饭了?
Carol: Mum wants to know if you are sure you don't want any dinner?
杰森:不吃.
Jason: No.
开萝尔:妈妈!他在生气.
Carol: Mum!He's pouting.
本:嗨,爸爸.
Ben: Hey dad.Do you mind if I watch the women's wrestling before I buckle
你介意我先看女子摔跤,然后认真学习呢?
down and study?
杰森:不介意.
Jason: Nope.
电视:女士们,先生们.
TV: Ladies and gentleman.Particularly the gentlemen.
尤其是先生们.这个我喜欢叫它摔个大背包.
That's what I like to call a leg lock.
杰森:本,你有没有感兴趣的事情,
Jason: Ben is there anything that you are interested in that you might
你需要我的帮忙吗?
want me to encourage?
本:没有.
Ben: Nothing.
杰森:本,答应我,
Jason: Ben promise me that they day will never come that you will stop
你永远听我的话?好吗?
listening to me?Ok?
本:啊?
Ben: Hu?
电视:没有动作规定吗?
TV: Are there no rules of decency?
杰森:说真的,女子摔跤有点分散我,本.走!
Jason: Actually this women's wrestling is a little distracting Ben.Go!
克莉丝:嗨,爸爸!
Chrissy: Hi Daddy.
杰森:嗨,小甜心.
Jason: Hi sweetheart.
克莉丝:我一直在想,我想成为像迈克那样的演员.
Chrissy: I've been thinking, I want to be an actress like Mike.
杰森:啊?
Jason: Hu?
克莉丝:妈妈让我这样说的.
Chrissy: Mum put me up to it.
麦琪:谢谢你,小甜心.
Maggie: Thank you sweetheart.
克莉丝:没什么.我乐意干.
Chrissy: It's ok.I enjoyed it.
麦琪:小甜心,我只是想证明事情可能会更糟.
Maggie: Sweetheart, I merely wanted to demonstrate that things could be worse.
杰森:亲爱的,我们失去了他.
Jason: Honey we've lost him.I mean he's never going to go back to school.
他永远不会再上学.他不会获得学位了.
he's not going to get an education.
我是说,也许这工作能干上一年,
I mean sure, maybe this job will last a year, two years, maybe three years.
两年或者三年.但是然后他做什么呢?
But then what is he going to do?
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,你该有点信心.
Maggie: Oh honey, you should have a little faith.
我是说,也许,也许,
I mean maybe, maybe, he'll be a celebrity.
他会成为名人.我是说,
I mean there is always a call for someone to open a supermarket,
需要有人去开超级市场,或主持选美比赛,或者当婚庆仪仗队司仪.
or host a beauty pageant, or be a grand martial of a parade.
杰森:那样叫作生活?
Jason: Call that a life?
麦琪:我知道,我知道.我和你一样难过.
Maggie: I know, I know.I feel as badly as you do.
但是,也许不会像你这么难受,因为这不是我的主意.
well, maybe not as bad a you do because it wasn't my hair brained idea.
电视:告诉你们,今晚我才明白.
TV: I'll tell you what I've learned tonight.
一旦被女人发现弱点,她会揪住不放.
Once a woman finds a weakness, she jumps all over it.
女人:如果你不站稳,
Lady: If you don't hold still,
你就会被大头针扎在某个地方,
you are likely to get a pin stuck some place that could be detrimental
这就对你男主角的职业有害了.
to your career as a leading man.
迈克:男主角.
Mike: A leading man.
女人:你好了.
Lady: You're done.
迈克:谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
凯特:他在那.
Kate: There he is.
保安:没有证件的话,你想去什么地方?
Security guard: Anywhere else you'd like to go without a pass?
我带你去.
I'll take you there.
凯特:那谢谢了,戴夫.
Kate: Well thank you Dave.
保安:不是我的名字,不是我的衬衫.
Security Guard: Not my name, not my shirt.
凯特:迈克!
Kate: Mike!
迈克:凯特,你好,真吃惊!见到你真好.
Mike: Kate hi, what a surprise!Good to see you.
凯特:我只是想告诉你,我真替你高兴.
Kate: I just wanted to tell you I am so happy for you.
迈克:哦,谢谢.谢谢.
Mike: Oh thank you.Thank you.
凯特:沙利文店里的那伙人昨晚把"在百老汇"献给了你.
Kate: The gang at Sullivan's dedicated "on Broadway" to you last night.
迈克:哦,真的吗?
Mike: Oh really.
凯特:一颗星.你在肥皂剧里正成名.
Kate: A star.You are starring on a soap opera.
迈克:我知道.我也不相信这样.
Mike: I know.I can't believe it either.
凯特:哦,这提醒我了.
Kate: Oh that reminds me.
迈克:圣诞树上的装饰?
Mike: A Christmas tree ornament?
凯特:不.给你化装间里的用的一颗星星.
Kate: No.It's a star for your dressing room.
迈克:哦,谢谢你,凯特.
Mike: Oh thank you Kate.Hey hey hey look.
嘿嘿嘿,听着.我真对不起我对你发火.
I'm really sorry I got mad at you.and just for the record, you were right.
而且我郑重声明,你是对的.
I mean I really should have told you Dad that I was ducking that class
我是说,我真的早就该告诉我爸爸,我三个月以来一直没有上课.
three months ago.
凯特:米歇尔,我确实相信你长大了.
Kate: Michael, I do believe you are growing up.
迈克:凯特,你还记得那个老片子里的电视演员,
Mike: Kate, do you remember that television actor on that old show, uh,
啊,?
Law Force?
凯特:记得,那个肩膀宽的那个?
Kate: Yeah, the eon e with the broad shoulders?
迈克:不,不,不.
Mike: No, no, no.The one with the cute butt.Lionel Douglas.
那个屁股可爱的.来昂内尔 道格拉斯.你想见他吗?
Do you want to meet him?
凯特:他在这?
Kate: He's here?
迈克:是的,他是我的一个伙伴.他也在这个片子里出演一个角色.
Mike: Yeah, he's a buddy of mine.
我想,他也会成功的.嗨,
He was going for a role in the same show.
来昂内尔!伙计!你还好?
I guess it worked out for him too.Hey Lionel!My man!How's it going?
来昂内尔:你是谁?
Lionel: Who are you?
迈克:你记得昨天的试演?
Mike: You remember yesterday at the audition?
来昂内尔:哦,是的,不错.你是西维尔小子.
Lionel: Au yes, that's right.You are the Seaver kid.
迈克:对了.
Mike: That's right.
来昂内尔:我知道你在里得到一个角色.
Lionel: I understand you got the role of Strom Waverly.
迈克:第三部.是,那么你得到什么角色?第二部?
Mike: The third.Yes, so who did you get?The second?
来昂内尔:不正确.
Lionel: Not exactly.
女士:你是我的捣蛋鬼?
Lady: Are you my doofus?
来昂内尔:是的.角色太小了.我会看上去像傻子的.
Lionel: Yeah.It's too small.I'm going to look silly.
女士:我的工作完成了.
Lady: My job is done.
迈克:你,你演捣蛋鬼?
Mike: You, you're playing the doofus?
来昂内尔:是的.我的经纪人和我.
Lionel: Yeah.My agent and I.
我们谈论了这件事,我们决定现在我的职业所需要的是好的角色.
we both talked about this and we decided that what my career needs right
你知道,这样才能真正显示我能够演出的角色范围.
now is a good character role.You know, something that really shows my range.
迈克:哦.
Mike: Oh.Co is thought a big famous actor like you would be pretty bummed
我认为让你这样一个大明星出演这样一个什么都不是的角色一定很窝囊.
out over such a nothing part.
来昂内尔:你别得意,不过昙花一现.
Lionel: You smug little flash in the pan.
迈克:我说了什么?
Mike: What did I say?
来昂内尔:听着!我得接受这角色,
Lionel: Look!I got to take this job cos it's the only thing I got.
因为这是唯一的机会.但是别指望我会听进你的废话.
But don't expect I'm going to take any crap from you.
迈克:嗨,伙计.对不起.
Mike: Hey man.I'm sorry.
来昂内尔:是啊.唉,你告诉我,
Lionel: Yeah.Well come talk to me after you've won an EMI and no one will
hire you.And then come see me when everyone starts asking you who you
然后对我来说就是,开始有人问你,你以前是干什么的.
used to be.
凯特:迈克,这不是你的错.
Kate: Mike, it's not your fault.
迈克:伙计,他真的发火了.
Mike: Man, he was really upset.
凯特:我想他不是那个意思.我是说,
Kate: I don't think he meant it.
如果你成了大明星,
I mean I'm sure you'd say a lot of things you didn't mean if you were
最后却落得跑龙套,你也会说出许多你不想说的.
a big star and then ended up on the bottom.
迈克:嗨,我是迈克 西维尔,我来这……
Mike: Hi I'm Mike Seaver rand I'm here to...
接待:那里.
Receptionist: Over there.
女孩:哦!哇!哇!那个老片子.你是迈克 西维尔.
Girl: Oh!Wow!Wow!That old show Big City Secrets.You're Mike Seaver.
迈克:放松点,孩子,你会爆炸的.
Mike: Easy kid, you're going to explode.
女孩:哦,上帝.我爱那部片子.
Girl: Oh god.I loved that show.I never missed a single episode.
我没有错过一个场景.因为你,我进入演艺界.哦,
It was because of you I went into acting.Oh god, you are awesome.
上帝,你棒极了.你怎么回事?
What ever happened to you?
接待:行了!行了!谁在这试演僵尸这个角色?
Receptionist: Alright!Alright!Who is here to read for the part of the Gadabba?Girl: You!But a person who has starred in his own network series would never try out for a part so, so stiff.
女孩:你!但是一个人已经在他自己的电视连续剧里成名,
Girl: You!But a person who has starred in his own network series would
不会尝试这么,这么呆板的角色.
never try out for a part so, so stiff.
迈克:我也是这么想的.
Mike: That's what I thought too.
凯特:那么迈克,你想去哪里庆祝?
Kate: So Mike, where do you want to go celebrate?
迈克:我不知道.
Mike: I don't know.
凯特:嗨!忘掉你的星吧.
Kate: Hey!Forgot your star.
杰森:麦琪!麦琪!这马蹄蛋糕恩,恩很好.
Jason: Maggie!Maggie!This horseshoe cake is hmm, hmm good.
麦琪:那么你又有胃口了?
Maggie: So you got your appetite back?
Jason: Not only that Maggie, but I've got a new plan.I call it plan
B
麦琪:哦,不.
Maggie: Oh no.
杰森:不,不,
Jason: No, no, this isn't like plan A.That was kind of half baked.
这和计划A不同.那个是半熟的计划.
Not that it was a mistake.
还不是错误.
Cos I believe we had to go through plan A to get to where we are
我相信我们需要察看一下计划A,看看现在走到哪一步了.
now.
麦琪:那么那是在哪,杰森?
Maggie: And where is that Jason?
杰森:你一定会喜欢这个因为……而且这很简单,麦琪,很简单,
Jason: Well you are going to love this because....
简单.就像所有的好主意.圆.
and its simple Maggie, so simple, simplicity.Just like all great ideas.
以圆开始.方就颠簸.圆是……
the wheel.Starting with the wheel.Square was bumpy.Round was...
麦琪:说吧.
Maggie: Just say it.
杰森:好来!好!那个想法,
Jason: Ok.Ok the idea Maggie; we pay Mike to go to school.
麦琪;我们付钱给迈克让他上学.我知道,我知道.
I know I know.I couldn't speak when I thought of it either.
我想到这个的时候,我也不想说出来.我们需要节省一些开支了,麦琪.
We just have to cut back on a few things Maggie.No more expensive dresses.
不买昂贵的时装,不去美容院做头发,以及不买昂贵的珠宝.
No more visits to the hair salon.No more expensive jewelry.
麦琪:啊哈.那么你想付给迈克多少钱让他去上学?
Maggie: Uh hu.And how much are you prepared to pay Mike to go to school?
杰森:我们的每一分钱.你怎么想的?
Jason: Every cent that we have.What do you think?
麦琪:杰森,你再一次这么做了.
Maggie: Jason, you have done it again.
杰森:是的.好了,你想和我一起告诉他这个新消息吗?
Jason: Yeah.Right, do you want to be part of telling him this new idea.
麦琪:不,不,不,我不想在今后的法律问题上失去底牌.
Maggie: No, no, no.I don't want to lose the basis for any future legal action.
迈克:爸爸.嗨,你有时间吗?
Mike: Dad.Hey, you got a minute?
杰森:是的,我有时间,迈克.
Jason: Yeah I do Mike.I do.
我有时间.实际上我正想和你谈谈呢.哦,
As a matter of fact I kind of wanted to talk to you.
关于我腰的事情.瞧,我在想.
Oh issue of my loins.See I've been thinking.
迈克:我在想.
Mike: I've been thinking.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
迈克:不,你先.
Mike: No, go ahead.
杰森:我先说.好吧,
Jason: Go ahead first.Ok, I'll go first.
我先说.迈克,你想不想在家里挣得很多很多的钱?
Mike, how would you like to make some big, big money at home?
迈克:啊,那,
Mike: Uh, well, I really don't know if I'm going to have any time between
我真的不知道我在工作和读书之间有没有时间,
my job and school.
杰森:但是听我说完,迈克,我想你会抽出时间的,因为你……你说什么呢?你说上学是什么意思呀?
Jason: But just hear me out Mike, and I think you are going to make time because you...what do you mean?What do you mean school?
迈克:是的.我正想跟你谈这事呢,
Mike: Yeah.That's what I wanted to talk to you about dad.
爸爸.你知道,恩,
You see um, I've really been thinking, and I've been thinking, you know,
我真的一直在想,我一直在想,
I guess it couldn't hurt to, to, go back and finish college.
你知道,我想我回去读完大学也没什么坏处.你知道,
You know, I mean, I'm really not going to be that busy.
我是说,我真的不会那么忙.
Cos the soap opera I'm working on has got sixteen leading men,
因为我演的那部肥皂剧里有16个男主角,我演的那个角色要过两三个星期才能苏醒过来,
and my character's not really coming out of a coma for the next two or
而且另外,演戏是,演戏是也没什么保障.
three months.And besides, acting is, acting is really not that secure.
而且我认为,我应该学些能靠得住的东西.
And I think I should have something to fall back on.
杰森:你在嘲笑我,是吗?迈克.
Jason: You're mocking me aren't you Mike?
杰森:不.不.
Mike: No.No.Dad, I'm not.Really.
爸爸.我没有.真的.
I mean that I think I've finally got what you've been saying to me all
我是说,我想我最终明白了这段时间你一直说的有安全感的意思.
this time about having a little security.
杰森:你最终明白了,是什么意思呀?
Jason: What do you mean you're finally just getting it now?
迈克:爸爸,对不起没有立即听你的.
Mike: Dad, I'm just sorry I didn't listen to you sooner.
杰森:好啊.好.
Jason: Well uh, ok.
迈克:那么啊,你说在家挣很多很多钱是什么呀?
Mike: Well uh, what were you saying about big big bucks at home?
杰森:哦,那是家务活,你知道的.比如除草,最低工资.
Jason: Oh, that was chores, you know.Mowing the lawn, minimum wage.
迈克:哦.啊.
Mike: Oh.Hu.
杰森:麦琪!迈克回去上大学了.
Jason: Maggie!Mike's going back to college.Ahooga chacku yeah yeah!
麦琪:确切地说,你去上学,我们付给你多少呀?
Maggie: Exactly how much are we paying you to go back to school?
迈克:付钱给我去上学?杰森:是的,
Mike: Paying me to go to school?
那是一个你妈妈的不成熟的想法.00:21:41,100
Jason: Yeah, that was one of your mother's half baked ideas.